Guide to the WHCU Department of Black Affairs records, 1971-1991.
WHCU Department of Black Affairs records, 1971-1991.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
WHCU Department of Black Affairs records, 1971-1991.
4904
WHCU Department of Black Affairs.
.1 cubic ft.; 173 tape recordings.
Tape recordings and scripts.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Tape recordings and scripts of the Night Sounds program broadcast on radio station WHCU in Ithaca, New York; interviews, promotional advertisements for local businesses, local news broadcasts, and other programs for the African American listening audience in Central New York State.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Tape recordings and scripts of the Night Sounds program broadcast on radio station WHCU in Ithaca, New York; interviews, promotional advertisements for local businesses, local news broadcasts, and other programs for the African American listening audience in Central New York State.
SUBJECTS
Names:
WHCU.
Subjects:
African American mass media--New York (State)--Ithaca.; African American radio stations--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Form and Genre Terms:
Tape recordings.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions
Restricted Files:
Series III: Box 3, Folder 41, "Letters Received 1975 - 1976"
Series III: Box 3, Folder 43, "Letters Received 1977 - 1979"
Series III: Box 3, Folder 45, "Letters Received 1979 - 1980"
Series III: Box 2, Folder 2, "Letters Received 1981"
Series III: Box 2, Folder 4, "Letters Received 1982"
Series III: Box 2, Folder 6, "Letters Received 1983"
Series III: Box 2, Folder 8, "Letters Received 1984"
Series III: Box 2, Folder 10, "Letters Received 1985 - 1986"
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Tape Recordings
  - N.S. Reel 1 - Homemakers Committee, Mar. 5, 1991; 7014
  - N.S. Reel 2, 7015
  - N.S. Reel 3, 7016
  - N.S. Reel 4, 7017
  - Night Sounds Production Tape, Feb. 19, 1991; 7018
  - N.S. Reel 6 - Backgrounds of Afro/Latino Sounds, Feb. 19, 1991; 7019
  - Puerto Rico and American Justice; N.S. Reel 7, Feb. 25, 1991; 7020
  - N.S. Reel 8, Soweto - Rest of the News, 7021
  - N.S. Reel 9, Bob Staples/J. Turner Interview, 7022
  - N.S. Reel 10- Dimension Series: "Black Students at Ithaca High School", Feb. 26, 1991; 7023
  - N.S. Reel 11 - Owusu Sadarkai, 7024
  - N.S. Reel 12 - The Oriental Bros., 7025
  - N.S. Reel 13 - Production Tape, 7026
  - N.S. Reel 14 - "Elks Rest" Farewell Reception for Lynn M. Harvey, Aug. 23, 1984; 7027
  - N.S. Reel 15 - Reel 3 - White Roots, 7028
  - N.S. Reel 16 Black History Month 1984, 7029
  - N.S. Reel 17 Bobby Byrd Blk Ivory Interview, 7030
  - N.S. Reel 18, 7031
  - N.S. Reel 19, 7032
  - N.S. Reel 20 Black Affairs Dept. Special, Dominica Special, Oct. 17, 1972; 7033
  - N.S. Reel 21 Native People's Program, 1-Apr-84; 7034
  - N.S. Reel 22, 7035
  - N.S. Reel 23 "Come Back Elena" and "In the Cutting of a Drink", 7036
  - N.S. Reel 24 "The Village Saint" and "A Crooked Rib", 7037
  - N.S. Reel 25 "A Kind of marriage", Mar. 28, 1991; 7038
  - N.S. Reel 26 "The Old Man of Usumbura" and "The Sun Roasted Me", Mar. 28, 1991; 7039
  - N.S. Reel 27 "The Barbed Wire" Part 1, 7040
  - N.S. Reel 28 "The Barbed Wire" Part 2, 7041
  - N.S. Reel 29 "Oda Oak Oracle" Part 2, 7042
  - N.S. Reel 30 "Oda Oak Oracle" Part 1, 7043
  - N.S. Reel 31 Prof. Murapa interview - The Next Vietnam, 7044
  - N.S. Reel 32 Saake; State of Black America, Apr. 20, 1982; June 25, 1991; 7045
  - N.S. Reel 33 The Seven Days of Kwanza, Dec. 26, 1981; 7046
  - N.S. Reel 34 Black World Newscast, July 24, 1980; 7047
  - N.S. Reel 35 Reaves, Eagle Bay - Indian Encampment for I.V.P., June 28, 1991; 7048
  - N.S. Reel 36 James Newton Premiere I.D./Promo, 7049
  - N.S. Reel 37 Silver Hill Recording, Nov. 12, 1979; 7050
  - N.S. Reel 38 History Reports 1-5, Sept.-Oct. 1979; 7051
  - N.S. Reel 39 Ojeda (oh-jay-dah) Penn, "South Afica"; Finger Lakes National Forest; Arcade and Attica Railroad; Fulton Fish Market Tours, Aug. 1988; 7052
  - N.S. Reel 40, 7053
  - N.S. Reel 41 Leslie Gross Dubbs, 7054
  - N.S. Reel 42 Leslie Gross Dubbs, 1982; 7055
  - N.S. Reel 43 Wanda Motley's "State of Black America" Campaign 1980, 1980; 7056
  - N.S. Reel 44, 7057
  - N.S. Reel 45 The State of Black America Segment: Black in the Military Part II, 7058
  - N.S. Reel 46 Linda Gadsby BWN Air Checks, 7059
  - N.S. Reel 47 Dizzy Gillespie Focus Part I, Sept. 30, 1982; 7060
  - N.S. Reel 48 Native People's Program, Mar. 4, 1984; 7061
  - N.S. Reel 49 Arnold Stovell Black World News Dubs, 7062
  - N.S. Reel 50 Ken Glover Black World News Air Checks, June 3, 1991; 7063
  - N.S. Reel 51 Sonji Stevenson Black World News Air Checks Reel I, June 3, 1991; 7064
  - N.S. Reel 52 Black History Month Promo Take #6, Feb. 1981; 7065
  - N.S. Reel 53 Annette I.D.'s/In the nightlight line Black World News In and Out, 7066
  - N.S. Reel 54 Tellin' It Like It Was Black American Poetry, D. Alexander, Feb. 14, 1983; 7067
  - N.S. Reel 55 Black History Month, 1985; 7068
  - N.S. Reel 56 Native People's Program, 7069
  - N.S. Reel 57, 7070
  - N.S. Reel 58 Kwanza, Day VII Imani, May 30, 1991; 7071
  - N.S. Reel 59 Mystery Theater, Nov. 15, 1982; 7072
  - N.S. Reel 60 Ebony Insight, May 30, 1941; 7073
  - N.S. Reel 61 Stan Reaves, 1975; 7074
  - N.S. Reel 62 American Music, 7075
  - N.S. Reel 63 Songi Stevenson BWN Air Checks Reel II, June 30, 1991; 7076
  - N.S. Reel 64 Cynthia Nwizu Dubb Tape, Nov. 1983; 7077
  - N.S. Reel 65 News Clips and Commercials; Air Check or ...Kim francis, Feb. 28, 1991; 7078
  - N.S. Reel 66 News Clips, Feb. 19, 1991; 7079
  - N.S. Reel 67 News Clips; "Tellin' It Like It Was", Feb. 25, 1991; 7080
  - N.S. Reel 68 Amanda Hor N.A.R. Minority Intern, Spring 1984; 7081
  - N.S. Reel 69Stokley Carmichael - Todd's Editorial, Mar. 5, 1984; Mar. 4, 1991; 7082
  - Commercials, Feb. 18, 1991; 7083
  - Community Day Celebration - Weekend Promo - Geo. Raymond - Old BWN, 1982; 7084
  - PSA and Commercial Dubs, Aug. 1976-Feb. 1977; 7085
  - take 11/commercials, Feb. 26, 1991; 7086
  - Ann Walters PSA Tape - Minority Radio Media Round-up, June 26, 1984; 7087
  - News Clips, Music and commercials, Stan Reaves Night Sounds - Temptations, DD Sharp, etc., Mar. 4, 1991; 7088
  - MusicAlice, "The Wizard", Mar. 4, 1991; Sept. 1985; 7089
  - 30 seconds of music, Mar. 4, 1991; 7090
  - Tshaka Tuner BWN Air Checks; Music/commercialsTshaka Tuner BWN Air Checks, Mar. 5, 1991; 7091
  - L-9-1-64, Mar. 5, 1991; 7092
  - D.B.A. Commercials and promosMusic and Commercials, 1975; Mar. 5, 1991; 7093
  - Music of Night Sounds, Mar. 25, 1991; 7094
  - Commercial, Mar. 25, 1991; 7095
  - blank tape, June 3, 1991; 7096
  - Trial: L. Gadsby Part IIMusic, Nov. 14, 1985; June 3, 1991; 7097
  - Tellin' It Like It WasPromos, May 2, 1983; June 3, 1991; 7098
  - "Han Yun"Sports, May 1, 1983; June 4, 1991; 7099
  - Trial: L. Gadsby Pt. IMusic, Nov. 14, 1985; June 6, 1991; 7100
  - Music, June 25, 1991; 7101
  - Charles Fabius BWN Air ChecksMusic Promos, June 25, 1991; 7102
  - Blank, June 25, 1991; 7103
  - Nightsounds Commercial DubsPromos, 1984-1986; June 25, 1991; 7104
  - Nightsounds Best of 1985Music, Dec. 31, 1985; July 2, 1991; 7105
  - Tellin" It Like It WasSingle Life The Best of 1985 Tape #2Music, Apr. 30, 1984; 1985; July 2, 1991; 7106
  - Tellin' It Like It WasNightsounds - The Best of 1985 "Dancing in the Key of Life"Music, Feb. 20, 1984; 1985; July 2, 1991; 7107
  - Best of 1985 "Saving All My Love"Music 1985, 1985; July 2, 1991; 7108
  - Music, Feb. 6, 1991; 7137
  - Displaced Homemakers Committee Job Readiness Training Program - Hazal Brampton, May 25, 1982; 7138
  - Music, Feb. 6, 1991; 7139
  - Night Sounds - 10th Anniversary, Feb. 6, 1991; 7140
  - Music and Commercials, Feb. 6, 1991; 7141
  - African - Slaves History, Feb. 6, 1991; 7142
  - Music, Feb. 10, 1991; 7143
  - Music, Feb. 10, 1991; 7144
  - African/American Sports News, Feb. 10, 1991; 7145
  - K. Crenshaw, Feb. 10, 1991; 7146
  - Ebony Insight, Feb. 11, 1991; 7147
  - Sports, Fights, Black World News, Feb. 11, 1991; 7148
  - Black World News/Clips, Feb. 11, 1991; 7149
  - Promo, June 25, 1991; 7150
  - Promo, June 25, 1991; 7151
  - Promo, June 26, 1991; 7152
  - Promo, June 26, 1991; 7153
  - The State of Black America Segment: Blacks in the Military - Fred Ennis, 7154
  - Dennis W[?] School Board Candidate on his campaign strategy and reaching the people, 7155
  - Black World News - Promo, June 26, 1991; 7156
  - Sports, June 26, 1991; 7157
  - Music - Night Sounds Promo Project Ennis, June 27, 1991; 7158
  - Dr. Martin Luther King Special, May 1979; 7159
  - Promo, June 28, 1991; 7160
  - Sports, June 30-July 4, 1991; 7161
  - Business Reports 1-5, 7162
  - Black Solidarity Day, 7163
  - Common Ground Production; George Byron Production, 7164
  - Johnson Products Company"Great Beautiful Black Women", 7165
  - NS/Jamaa, Sept. 4, 1979; 7166
  - Teletype for news production, 7167
  - "Blank - found nothing on this tape", 7168
  - Sall Show This Week, 7169
  - Night Sounds Tee Shirts Master (Promo), 7170
  - Series 93 Business Reports 1-5, 7171
  - Business Reports 1-5, 7172
  - Series 29 History Reports 1-5, 7173
  - Series 24 Sport Reports 1-5, 7174
  - Series 24 Business Reports, July 1979; 7175
- Series I. Office Files
  - Budget Reports, 1974 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Department Proposals (Folder 1 of 2), 1974 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Department Proposals (Folder 2 of 2), 1974 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Intros, Outros, Promos and Dubs (Folder 1 of 2), 1982 - 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Intros, Outros, Promos and Dubs (Folder 2 of 2), 1982 - 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Job Descriptions, 1978 - 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Nightsounds Alumni Folder (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Nightsounds Announcer Information (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Nightsounds Announcer Information (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Nightsounds Announcers' Manual (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Nightsounds Staff, 1978, 1981 - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Nightsounds Surveys (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Nightsounds Surveys (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Program Promotion (Folder 1 of 2), 1974 - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Program Promotion (Folder 2 of 2), 1974 - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Reports on Activities, 1975 - 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Staff Resumes (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Student Internships, 1979 - 1980, 1983 - 1984 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Student Work/Study, 1981 - 1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Black History Month: Black Writers, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Series II. Special Projects
  - Black History Month: Celebrating the Strength, Spirit and Courage of Black Women (Folder 1 of 2), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Black History Month: Celebrating the Strength, Spirit and Courage of Black Women (Folder 2 of 2), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Black History Month (Folder 1 of 2), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Black History Month (Folder 2 of 2), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Black History Month (Folder 1 of 2), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Black History Month (Folder 2 of 2), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Black History Month, 1980 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Black World News Editorials, 1979 - 1984 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Black World News - Press Releases, 1978 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Black World News Sources, 1978 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Black World News Special Projects, 1982 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ebony Insight, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Ebony Insight (Folder 1 of 2), 1981 - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Ebony Insight (Folder 2 of 2), 1981 - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Ebony Insight (Folder 1of 2), 1978 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Ebony Insight (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Special Projects (Folder 1 of 2), 1981 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Special Projects (Folder 2 of 2), 1981 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Westwood One Productions - "Tellin' it like it was...", 1982 - 1984 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Series III. Correspondence
  - Letters Received, 1975 - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Letters Received, 1975 - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Letters Received, 1977 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Letters Received (Restricted), 1977 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Letters Received, 1979 - 1980 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Letters Received (Restricted), 1979 - 1980 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Letters Received, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Letters Received (Restricted), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Letters Received, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Letters Received (Restricted), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Letters Received, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Letters Received (Restricted), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Letters Received, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Letters Received (Restricted), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Letters Received, 1985 - 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Letters Received (Restricted), 1985 - 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Series IV. Subject Files
  - African News, 1976 - 1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Allan Bakke Case, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Black and Puerto Rican Legislative Caucus, 1975 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Black Men of Ithaca, 1975 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Black Alumni, 1967 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - COSEP (Folder 1 of 2), 1975 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - COSEP (Folder 2 of 2), 1975 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Drive to Save NightSounds, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Elmira Prison Project, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Herb Parker Firing/Day Hall Takeover, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - History of Black Radio in Ithaca - "NightSounds", 1974 - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - History of Black Radio in Ithaca - "Sounds of Blackness" (Folder 1 of 2), 1972 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - History of Black Radio in Ithaca - "Sounds of Blackness" (Folder 2 of 2), 1972 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - History of Blacks in Ithaca (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Ku Klux Klan Activity (Includes Press Releases and Black World News Stories), 1979 - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - NAACP File of Press Releases, 1983 - 1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - National Black Independence Political Party, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Sambo's Restaurant Controversy, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - South Africa, 1978 - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Tenth Anniversary Celebration, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Assorted writing, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)